Guide to the Class of 1935 records,1929-1995.
Class of 1935 records,1929-1995.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Class of 1935 records, 1929-1995.
41\4\3430
Cornell UniversityClass of 1935.
2 cubic ft.
Memorabilia, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photograph albums documenting reunions of the Class of 1935; slides of class activities, 1976-1981; and movie films. Also records relating to Reunions and to the Class of 1935 Walk.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photograph albums documenting reunions of the Class of 1935; slides of class activities, 1976-1981; and movie films. Also records relating to Reunions and to the Class of 1935 Walk.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University.Class of 1935.
Subjects:
Student activities.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Four Phi Kappa Psi members [photocopy], n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Fragments [photocopy], 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Files and photos, 1960-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meetings, Reunions, 1970-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
- R. Katzenstein: Reunion photos, 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
- Files, 1982-1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Files, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Reunion correspondence and files, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Reunion photos, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Reunions, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reunion and class files, 1987-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 55th Reunion, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Files, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Reunion files, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16-18)
- James Andrew Mullane: Class materials, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
- Slides: Class dinner, NYC, 1976 (Box 1)
- Art North: Mini Reunions, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Slides: Cornell Club: Dartmouth at Boston, 1977 (Box 2)
- Slides: 45th Reunion, 1980 (Box 2)
- Slides: Reunion, 1981 (Box 2)
- Unidentified film, n.d. (Box 2)
- Dan & Esther Bondareff: photo album: Reunions, 1981-1985 (Box 2)
- Reel-to-reel audio tape: Reunion: Gordon Jenkins, n.d. (Box 2)
- Slides: Dartmouth Weekend at Bo's and Homecoming Ithaca - Johnson Museum, 1979 (Box 2)